zeekler.com 2011-06-28

# Privacy Policy - Zeekler

Zeekler.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Zeekler.com.

##    
Information Collection and Use 

Zeekler is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Zeekler collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

##    
Registration 

During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. Passwords are collected to verify the user's identity. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information, but the user is encouraged to do so, so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

##    
Purchases

This Site uses order forms for customers to purchase products, and services. We collect customers' financial information (like their account number, billing address or credit card numbers). This information is used to bill the customer for products and services. If we have trouble processing an order, this information is used to contact the customer. 

##    
Cookies 

A cookie is personalized data on a user's computer that we use to keep track of that user's information. For example, when the user signs in, a cookie lets us remember who the user is. We set a cookie so that users can access their account without login in every time. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user may not be able to administer his/her account. Cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

##    
Log Files 

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

##    
Sharing 

We use credit card processing companies to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

When permission is provided, we share personally identifiable information with selected partners for the purpose of email delivery on topics that the user signed up for. 

##    
Links and Ads 

We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

##    
Security 

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. 

This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our data center uses a wide range of physical security features, including state-of-the-art smoke detection and fire suppression systems, motion sensors, and 24x7 secured access, as well as guards, video camera surveillance and security breach alarms. 

##    
Account Information

We send the user financial account notices (such as monthly statements or overdue invoices). Users are not able to un-subscribe from these notices, which contain important information about their account. We communicate issues relating to their account via email, fax, USPS and phone. In certain cases, account information may be shared with collection agents.

##    
Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done at the user's Account Administration page or by contacting Technical Support. 

##    
Notification of Changes 

If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
